<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel xmlns:os="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/"><title>“designer, frontend” jobs - Stack Overflow Careers</title><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs</link><description>“designer, frontend” jobs - Stack Overflow Careers</description><os:totalResults>35</os:totalResults><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114164/frontend-developer-designer-fielmann-ventures</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114164/frontend-developer-designer-fielmann-ventures</link><a10:author><a10:name>Fielmann Ventures</a10:name></a10:author><category>html5</category><category>javascript</category><category>sass</category><category>less</category><category>css</category><title>Frontend Developer / Designer at Fielmann Ventures (Hamburg, Germany)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you&amp;nbsp;share our passion for functional design, holistic design thinking and are you&amp;nbsp;an expert in web front-end development?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Fielmann Ventures, we design the future of the optical industry. As a Frontend&amp;nbsp;Developer, you will be part of a multi-disciplinary team and help us build&amp;nbsp;prototypes for&amp;nbsp;innovative customer-facing products. Your focus lies on bringing static design to life by&amp;nbsp;adding motion design, adapting it to different media and implementing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;strong&gt;design-centric&amp;nbsp;position&lt;/strong&gt; that requires experience in both design &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; programming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bridge the gap between design and engineering by implementing interactive user&amp;nbsp;interfaces based on existing static designs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adapt design concepts to different media by making it responsive, by adding motion&amp;nbsp;design or by deviating from the standard where necessary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quickly adapt to various media such as desktops, showroom TVs, handhelds, tablets, or even VR and AR systems, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapidly prototype user interfaces to make innovative business ideas tangible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement pixel perfect frontends in HTML 5, JavaScript and related technologies to&amp;nbsp;deliver a beautiful interactive customer experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please provide a portfolio of designs you have created and/or adapted along with your application.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:22:23 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-20T11:22:23Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Hamburg, Germany</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114275/web-designer-formlabs</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114275/web-designer-formlabs</link><a10:author><a10:name>Formlabs</a10:name></a10:author><title>Web Designer at Formlabs (Somerville, MA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To reinvent an industry, you have to build the best team. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join Formlabs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; if you want to bring ground-breaking professional 3D printers to the desktop of every &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;designer, engineer, researcher, and artist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formlabs&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; web team designs, develops and maintains a suite of applications for internal and customer-facing use. W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;e&amp;rsquo;re looking for a talented Web Designer to create an elegant, scalable and user-friendly experience. If you have an eye for clean design and a sensitivity to user-system interaction, we have the perfect challenge for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us as a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Designer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and help us grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Job:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Design web pages and content; rely on a keen understanding of user needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contribute to Formlabs&amp;rsquo; brand development--in a major way (our website is key)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ensure that Formlabs&amp;rsquo; web content is responsive across digital and mobile form&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborate across web and marketing teams, and work closely with other web specialists (developers and graphic designers) to produce high-quality creative work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 20:46:21 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-20T20:46:21Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Somerville, MA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/108344/frontend-dev-gecko-health-innovations-inc</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/108344/frontend-dev-gecko-health-innovations-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>Gecko Health Innovations Inc.</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>angularjs</category><category>jquery</category><category>css3</category><category>html5</category><title>Frontend Dev at Gecko Health Innovations Inc. (Cambridge, MA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gecko was recently&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;acquired&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;by the leading generics pharmaceutical company in the world to be their nucleus for innovative e-health platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are expected to be able to communicate effectively with other engineers, as well as product and design teams. Ultimately, you are passionate about designing products that emphasize your expertise in user experience definition and user interface design. Our client applications include native iOS and Android applications as well as multiple browser interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are both creative &amp;amp; analytical.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 19:42:32 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-05T19:42:32Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Cambridge, MA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114226/senior-frontend-engineer-m-f-for-a-finleap-finleap-gmbh</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114226/senior-frontend-engineer-m-f-for-a-finleap-finleap-gmbh</link><a10:author><a10:name>FinLeap GmbH</a10:name></a10:author><category>reactjs</category><category>angularjs</category><category>javascript</category><category>node.js</category><category>html5</category><title>Senior Frontend Engineer (m/f) for a FinLeap Venture at FinLeap GmbH (Berlin, Germany)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Role &amp;amp; Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are responsible for the leading the frontend development of a new product&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You develop a responsive UI design for a large user base&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You research new technologies and happy to learn new ones that will improve our products and development flow&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You work with our designers to create solutions that offer a good user experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You take responsibility to ensure successful results&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You work with different backend APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You work directly with the CTO&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Perfect Match:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You bring 4+ years experience in Frontend software engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience with React.js and willingness to innovate (experience with Angular.js is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working experience with JavaScript, advanced Javascript frameworks, Node.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with responsive web development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of MVC&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and SASS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very strong communication skills with external and internal stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytical way of thinking and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with CMS systems is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in security is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile related frameworks is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We empower entrepreneurs to reshape finance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A mix of serial entrepreneurs and industry experts work together to ensure each company&amp;rsquo;s success&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talented, dedicated and passionate people are at the core of our business&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We believe hard work and success deserve to be celebrated&amp;mdash;both in and out of the office&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested? - Submit your CV along with your GitHub Account to&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;jobs@finleap.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:58:45 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-20T11:58:45Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Berlin, Germany</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/72146/javascript-developer-front-end-web-chefsteps-inc</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/72146/javascript-developer-front-end-web-chefsteps-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>ChefSteps, Inc</a10:name></a10:author><category>angularjs</category><category>haml</category><category>sass</category><category>coffeescript</category><category>ionic-framework</category><title>JavaScript Developer - Front End Web at ChefSteps, Inc (Seattle, WA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At ChefSteps, we&amp;rsquo;re not just cooks&amp;mdash;we are engineers and designers; it&amp;rsquo;s as much a tech company as it is a culinary one.&amp;nbsp;We believe the future will be better when software helps cooks to learn from each other and powers the tools that put them in control of the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You could play a key role in making that vision a reality. See&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://blog.chefsteps.com/2013/09/a-word-to-the-geeks-what-we-are-building-at-chefsteps/" rel="nofollow"&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for some of the areas we are working on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced developer with a passion for frontend work. You have built complex web apps using AngularJS or another modern Javascript framework. You wouldn't dream of writing jQuery spaghetti in 2014. You create structured, modular CSS. You play nicely with designers and care about implementing pixel-perfect, responsive, jank-free interfaces - and you can send us the URLs to prove it. Bonus points if you've also built native-wrapped HTML5 apps using Cordova. You might be the right fit if you love food, are self-directed, enjoy refactoring, and are experienced enough to know how and when to ship.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 17:47:27 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-19T17:47:27Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Seattle, WA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/111842/frontend-engineer-studyblue-inc</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/111842/frontend-engineer-studyblue-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>StudyBlue Inc.</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html</category><category>css</category><category>backbone.js</category><category>jquery</category><title>Frontend Engineer at StudyBlue Inc. (San Francisco, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a talented, hard working human being who is hungry to do big things. &amp;nbsp;You&amp;rsquo;re an experienced software developer with a passion for building robust and efficient CSS/HTML/Javascript-based web applications. You consider the user experience, performance, and code maintainability all at the same time. You aren&amp;rsquo;t biased against writing your own code or using existing libraries and frameworks, depending on what each individual situation requires. You work well with others and are eager to use your experiences and skills to mentor teammates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and implement features in the Javascript-based StudyBlue web properties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enhance front-end architecture to improve performance, scalability, maintainability, and flexibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using browser diagnostics, find and fix errors and performance issues quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Designers to ensure visuals integrate well into a web environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Backend engineers to determine APIs, and glue API results into the data model&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Product to ensure the vision for the User Experience is achieved&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor junior engineers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Illustrate and diagram designs in a clear and concise fashion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 22:58:32 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-21T22:58:32Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">San Francisco, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113428/senior-frontend-engineer-globality</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113428/senior-frontend-engineer-globality</link><a10:author><a10:name>Globality</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html5</category><category>sass</category><category>angularjs</category><category>css3</category><title>Senior Frontend Engineer at Globality (Menlo Park, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Based in Menlo Park, CA, &lt;strong&gt;Globality, Inc&lt;/strong&gt;. is a stealth startup making globalization work for small and midsize companies using internet technology and human-curated AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supported by an impressive group of prominent investors, including Al Gore and Ron Johnson, and cofounded by serial entrepreneurs, Joel Hyatt and Lior Delgo, Globality is well-funded and poised for success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We seek &lt;strong&gt;Senior Frontend Engineers&lt;/strong&gt; who can design, deliver, and maintain compelling software-driven experiences. We believe that great software engineers are versatile generalists and are defined more by their &lt;em&gt;actions &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; judgment&lt;/em&gt; than the specific &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt; they know. As such, we value:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Owning delivery end-to-end and releasing without drama.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Treating team success as personal success.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Curiosity and translating learning into systematic improvement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thinking clearly and communicating effectively.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using the right tool for the job, especially open source. (Check out: &lt;a href="http://code.globality.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;code.globality.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 09:26:29 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-11T09:26:29Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Menlo Park, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113768/senior-javascript-engineer-react-gin-lane</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113768/senior-javascript-engineer-react-gin-lane</link><a10:author><a10:name>Gin Lane</a10:name></a10:author><category>reactjs</category><category>javascript</category><category>ecmascript-6</category><category>css3</category><category>animation</category><title>Senior Javascript Engineer (React) at Gin Lane (New York, NY)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a forward-thinking Senior Javascript Engineer to join our team. The ideal candidate will be a passionate thought-leader that is adept at creating elegant, future-facing experiences. They&amp;rsquo;ll be working closely with all disciplines in the product team to help create consumer-centric applications that are intelligent and alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Gin Lane, we&amp;rsquo;re dedicated to building the best consumer experiences in the world, through storytelling and technology. We believe that the best brands stand for something, and deliver a consistent experience of that belief across all of their touchpoints.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 11:03:48 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-14T11:03:48Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">New York, NY</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112795/web-ui-developer-portland-or-or-sf-bay-area-oportun</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112795/web-ui-developer-portland-or-or-sf-bay-area-oportun</link><a10:author><a10:name>Oportun</a10:name></a10:author><category>user-experience</category><category>user-interface</category><category>css3</category><category>html5</category><category>web-frontend</category><title>Web UI Developer - Portland, OR or S.F. Bay area ONLY at Oportun (Portland, OR)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT engineering @ Oportun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Engineering team @ Oportun (formerly Progreso Financiero) is dedicated to shipping performant, elegant, and intuitive software to our retail agents and directly to our customers.&amp;nbsp; We provide the platform, software services, and interfaces that have enabled Oportun to serve over 370,000 customers with over $1 billion in life-changing, responsible loans disbursed.&amp;nbsp; We work on a very unique platform, combining service-oriented platform services with sophisticated frontend user experiences, all enabled through a best-in-class (and fun to use!) automated development infrastructure.&amp;nbsp; We prove that FinTech is more fun, more challenging, and in our case, more rewarding as we build technology that changes our customers&amp;rsquo; lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We want to grow our front-end team by adding an experienced Web UI Developer.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; We&amp;rsquo;re looking not only for a proven engineer, but for a great team member--someone who is comfortable working with our product, platform, and design teams to bring the next step in our company vision to life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our team, we put a high degree of trust in our leaders to deliver against the commitments we make to each other and to our business partners. Therefore, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to demonstrate a high degree of accountability, the ability to spot a problem + own it to resolution and the ability to inspire others to cross the finish line strong.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 18:28:48 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-01T18:28:48Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Portland, OR</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113317/remote-us-based-frontend-designer-developer-dealer-inspire</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113317/remote-us-based-frontend-designer-developer-dealer-inspire</link><a10:author><a10:name>Dealer Inspire</a10:name></a10:author><category>frontend</category><category>javascript</category><category>angular</category><title>Remote (US-based) Frontend Designer/Developer at Dealer Inspire (Naperville, IL) (allows remote)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dealer Inspire is looking for an experienced developer to join our team. We're always innovating - we're looking for people that can own projects and see them through to delivery - while we want rock stars, we're not interested in prima donnas. Personal responsibility with respect to quality, attention to detail, and contribution of ideas is highly needed to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Dealer Inspire, we like to look at current problems and 'rethink' about solutions. We're flexible - we don't write requirements in stone, and things can change regularly. This means rethinking how the solutions work best. Do you want to come 'rethink' with us?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're flexible with learning on the job, with corresponding relevant work experience - but, for this position to be successful we need you to know the following, with a strong self-initiative to learn others!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong JavaScript skills - ie, not tweaking existing jQuery plugins, but the ability to dig in and drive a powerful user experience that supports the major browsers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong Sass/SCSS organizational skills. &amp;nbsp;You have a SCSS compiler preference, and defend it to the death.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to design detail. &amp;nbsp;Matching markup / layout with mockups, and making them better. &amp;nbsp;Knowing when things are off (even by a couple pixels) - and knowing why that impacts the experience negatively.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diagnosis skills. &amp;nbsp;Ability to dive into a reported problem and figure out why things are happening, and knowing what other factors are contributing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highly Desired:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some PHP - enough to be dangerous and be comfortable working with code from other backend engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Grunt/Gulp/etc - you'll own the frontend processes for how the code is managed on the browser. &amp;nbsp;We're flexible, but the reasoning needs to be backed by knowledge and understanding.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Dealer Inspire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dealer Inspire is an automotive website platform provider located in downtown Naperville, Illinois. We pride ourselves in having a fun, unconventional working environment and a great culture. While our team works extremely hard, we try to keep it a fun and creative work environment. We are located in the heart of downtown Naperville, IL, steps from great restaurants and a beautiful river walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compensation based upon skill and previous experience. Motivated and talented individuals may advance quickly in our fast growing company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% match of your 401k contributions up to 4% of your gross income&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 days paid time off, 5 days of sick/safe leave and selected paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work time/Fun time bi-monthly team outings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coaching and career building&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Subsidized gym membership&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Subsidized internet access for your home&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Benefits package including Health, Life, Dental, Vision, and Disability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 14:33:24 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-08T14:33:24Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Naperville, IL</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113225/frontend-developer-hlk</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113225/frontend-developer-hlk</link><a10:author><a10:name>HLK</a10:name></a10:author><category>csss3</category><category>html5</category><category>javascript</category><category>json</category><title>Frontend Developer at HLK (St. Louis, MO) (allows remote)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;HLK, a full-service digital agency with offices in St. Louis and Denver, is looking for a Front-End Developer in their St. Louis office responsible for building interactive websites, social media applications and responsive/mobile websites; someone with a passion for code, a desire to learn new technologies, and to share what you learn with others. You will work with other front-end and back-end developers, strategists and designers across the agency. The successful candidate will have a passion for digital advertising and an insatiable desire to learn and explore emerging trends as well as align with our core values: Be Curious, Be Thoughtful and Be Brave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideally, you will have a strong understanding of design fundamentals, user experience best practices, and typography &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;and a passion for putting those ideas to work on the screen. Projects will range from the transactional (targeted email marketing campaigns and conversion-oriented landing pages) to the communicative (brand websites and content-focused web publications) to the playful (immersive web experiences with animation and interactive narrative elements) and everything in-between. The ability to work in a team is a must and familiarity with agile development methods is a plus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Areas of Competence and Understanding:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with strategists, designers and developers to build responsive websites, web applications, and social media tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integrate content and markup into publishing platforms including Adobe Experience Manager, WordPress, and Sharepoint&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide input on emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform cross-browser testing and assist with QA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of responsive web design principles and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript (jQuery or Vanilla JS)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of how websites and applications communicate with each other via JSON, XML, AJAX, etc&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience connecting websites and social networks, including Facebook and Twitter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5 animation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with HTML5 video and audio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to shift between multiple projects and technologies quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 18:25:33 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-07T18:25:33Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">St. Louis, MO</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114412/senior-ui-engineer-practice-fusion</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114412/senior-ui-engineer-practice-fusion</link><a10:author><a10:name>Practice Fusion</a10:name></a10:author><category>ember.js</category><category>user-interface</category><category>frontend</category><category>html</category><category>agile</category><title>Senior UI Engineer at Practice Fusion (San Francisco, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Practice Fusion is looking for a talented Senior Front End Engineer who is passionate about creating life-saving technologies for doctors and patients. Our cloud-based&amp;nbsp;EHR&amp;nbsp;client is an ambitious Ember app that is used by tens of thousands of health providers on a daily basis, supported by a custom&amp;nbsp;component library add-on and an ember-cli build system.&amp;nbsp;You will be taking on the challenge of delivering robust production code across our entire front-end technology set and&amp;nbsp;building functional, responsive, and elegant user&amp;nbsp;interfaces that our users love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, test and maintain our core Ember&amp;nbsp;application&amp;nbsp;and add-ons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write high quality, well-tested, readable and maintainable code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with fellow developers, test engineers, UX designers, and product management to iterate on new features&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide technical leadership and mentoring for other UI engineers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introduce and evolve best-of-breed UI engineering methodologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deliver in a highly-agile,&amp;nbsp;cross-functional Scrum environment&lt;/li&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 22:37:00 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-21T22:37:00Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">San Francisco, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114522/senior-frontend-developer-tradeshift</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114522/senior-frontend-developer-tradeshift</link><a10:author><a10:name>Tradeshift</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>angularjs</category><category>reactjs</category><category>frontend</category><category>cloud</category><title>Senior Frontend Developer at Tradeshift (San Francisco, CA)</title><description>Tradeshift is looking for an outstanding Senior Frontend Developer with the skills to bring new products to market and improve our existing platform and products. You will have the opportunity to make a difference as we strive to connect all of the companies in the world and make business applications better for *people*. We believe in team-based component ownership, development, and quality assurance. We expect engineer involvement from product inception through production support. Our teams have great autonomy and responsibility to choose the best solutions, technologies, and approaches to bringing Tradeshift to the next level. Of course, this will not be easy; you will face a lot of complex challenges in our growing, global, fast-paced startup. &lt;strong&gt;Our Engagement Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;is building the world's largest B2B network where companies can connect, collaborate, transact and get insights. Tradeshift has 500,000+ users and is growing rapidly. &amp;nbsp;The Network team focuses on driving growth and engagement of the users on Tradeshift network providing them value and ways to share and collaborate with their business counterparts.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 23:20:12 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-22T23:20:12Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">San Francisco, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112866/web-ui-developer-oportun</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112866/web-ui-developer-oportun</link><a10:author><a10:name>Oportun</a10:name></a10:author><category>user-experience</category><category>user-interface</category><category>css3</category><category>html5</category><category>web-frontend</category><title>Web UI Developer at Oportun (Modesto, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT engineering @ Oportun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Engineering team @ Oportun (formerly Progreso Financiero) is dedicated to shipping performant, elegant, and intuitive software to our retail agents and directly to our customers.&amp;nbsp; We provide the platform, software services, and interfaces that have enabled Oportun to serve over 370,000 customers with over $1 billion in life-changing, responsible loans disbursed.&amp;nbsp; We work on a very unique platform, combining service-oriented platform services with sophisticated frontend user experiences, all enabled through a best-in-class (and fun to use!) automated development infrastructure.&amp;nbsp; We prove that FinTech is more fun, more challenging, and in our case, more rewarding as we build technology that changes our customers&amp;rsquo; lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We want to grow our front-end team by adding an experienced Web UI Developer.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; We&amp;rsquo;re looking not only for a proven engineer, but for a great team member--someone who is comfortable working with our product, platform, and design teams to bring the next step in our company vision to life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our team, we put a high degree of trust in our leaders to deliver against the commitments we make to each other and to our business partners. Therefore, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to demonstrate a high degree of accountability, the ability to spot a problem + own it to resolution and the ability to inspire others to cross the finish line strong.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 13:42:05 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-04T13:42:05Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Modesto, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110657/senior-javascript-developer-crystalcommerce</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110657/senior-javascript-developer-crystalcommerce</link><a10:author><a10:name>CrystalCommerce</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html5</category><category>css3</category><category>angularjs</category><category>php</category><title>Senior JavaScript Developer at CrystalCommerce (Mountlake Terrace, WA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;CrystalCommerce is looking for a skilled frontend web developer to join our awesome team of engineers and web designers! Make good design come alive with jQuery, Ajax, PHP, and other frontend technologies. Manipulate dynamic content and create interactive UI elements. Every project is an opportunity to solve a problem and provide a new solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At CrystalCommerce, we create websites that allow game and hobby store owners to showcase their products to millions of end users worldwide. &amp;nbsp;Our front end developers play an instrumental role in making sure the user experience is visually appealing and practical at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits Include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive Pay (This is a full-time, salaried position)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive Insurance - Medical/Dental/Vision Insurance after 60 days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;401(k) with company matching&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two weeks of paid vacation per year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;8 paid Holidays per year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible schedule&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Office Cats! We have two of them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pretty darn cool product&amp;hellip;we aren&amp;rsquo;t creating insurance software or anything like that&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Casual dress and atmosphere&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and develop websites for client and internal projects (web apps, e-commerce, marketing / campaign websites, etc).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support existing web applications including troubleshooting, bug fixing, required upgrades and modifications to existing functionality.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optimize web applications to maximize speed and scale; Identifying and addressing potential front end performance bottlenecks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work cross-departmentally with our engineering, member success, and design and branding teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 23:09:13 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-25T23:09:13Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Mountlake Terrace, WA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113797/interactive-news-developer-new-york-times</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113797/interactive-news-developer-new-york-times</link><a10:author><a10:name>New York Times</a10:name></a10:author><category>ruby</category><category>note</category><category>phyton</category><title>Interactive News Developer at New York Times (New York, NY)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Interactive News desk at The New York Times is looking for creative, interdisciplinary thinkers with strong technical backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interactive News is the special digital projects team embedded within the newsroom of The New York Times. You'll be working with editors, reporters, photographers, designers and other developers to create newsroom-facing tools and reader-facing projects that expand the horizons of our digital news report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our department&amp;rsquo;s goal is to practice web development and software engineering as a newsroom craft.&amp;nbsp; We draw on technical expertise to imagine new editorial forms. Most of our work is published in collaboration with other newsroom departments. Your role is to bring digital creativity and software expertise. Interactive News handles a mix of project types:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Early-stage experiments: You will iterate quickly and collaboratively to explore new ideas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;More mature projects: You will use engineering expertise to improve the scale and repeatability of our projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Library and tool development: You will package functionality so that it can be reused by others in the organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;No journalism experience is required, but you should enjoy thinking about how to create thoughtful experiences for our readers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You also have a strong sense of personal responsibility: You can be trusted to deliver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You take a creative approach to solving problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a strong technical skillset: You can take ownership of a high-quality digital experience from start to finish.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You enjoy working as part of a team but are self-disciplined when working alone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re comfortable jumping between details and bigger-picture challenges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you are a member of a group that has been historically underrepresented in technology, we especially encourage you to apply.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About our Tech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ruby, Node and Python are the team&amp;rsquo;s predominant backend technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;On the frontend, our projects are largely JavaScript (ES5+) and CSS (often SASS), with judicious use of ReactJS and similar project-appropriate libraries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deployment, testing and maintenance of projects are shared responsibilities. We currently deploy server-side code in Docker containers to a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You should have demonstrated experience in one of the areas above and be willing to build skills in the rest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have both backend-focused and frontend-focused roles available. From either perspective, you ideally would be comfortable working (or eager to learn to work) across the stack. In Interactive News, we want every team member to be comfortable making changes and pushing them live to the site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please provide:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Links to some work samples, e.g. sites you&amp;rsquo;ve worked on, your Github, or a portfolio site&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your r&amp;eacute;sum&amp;eacute;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A brief paragraph describing why you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the job and what you hope to get out of it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If interested, send us a resume at&amp;nbsp;newsdev-jobs@nytimes.com. &amp;nbsp;This is an excluded position.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 15:43:01 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-14T15:43:01Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">New York, NY</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113601/full-stack-software-developer-oneome</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113601/full-stack-software-developer-oneome</link><a10:author><a10:name>OneOme</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>linux</category><category>mysql</category><category>mongodb</category><category>jquery</category><title>Full Stack Software Developer at OneOme (Minneapolis, MN)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a Full Stack Software Developer to join an existing team of software developers and scientists that are building and supporting OneOme&amp;rsquo;s PGx solution. The ideal candidate will be well versed in building and maintaining full stack web applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At OneOme, our mission is to provide the most cost-effective, comprehensive, personalized, pharmacogenomics analysis at the point of care. This is an exciting space and we are partnered with the world renowned health institution Mayo Clinic. OneOme is a place where you can make a difference in the lives of many people.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 17:57:06 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-19T17:57:06Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Minneapolis, MN</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112807/frontend-developer-for-sex-ed-company-omgyes</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112807/frontend-developer-for-sex-ed-company-omgyes</link><a10:author><a10:name>OMGYes</a10:name></a10:author><category>angularjs</category><category>css3</category><category>html5</category><category>jquery</category><category>photoshop</category><title>Frontend Developer for Sex-Ed Company- demystifying pleasure with science at OMGYes (Berkeley, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a Front-End Web Developer who is motivated to combine the art of design with the art of programming. This person will be responsible for the creation of front-end UI/UX components and infrastructure for backend services. You will work with the UI/UX designer and bridge the gap between graphical design and technical implementation, taking an active role on both sides and defining how the application looks as well as how it works. You'll work with the systems administrator to keep the front-end in sync with backend database requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;* Develop new user-facing features&lt;br&gt;* Build reusable code and libraries for future use&lt;br&gt;* Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs&lt;br&gt;* Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;br&gt;* Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders&lt;br&gt;* Train a Junior Front-End Developer to handle basic site tasks&lt;br&gt;* Develop and maintain core JavaScript infrastructure&lt;br&gt;* Develop and maintain core HTML/CSS framework&lt;br&gt;* Act as HTML, CSS, and JS SME (subject matter expert) and provide advice and direction to other team-members&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 23:58:06 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-01T23:58:06Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Berkeley, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110710/front-end-engineer-enigma</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110710/front-end-engineer-enigma</link><a10:author><a10:name>Enigma</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>reactjs</category><category>html</category><category>css</category><title>Front-End Engineer at Enigma (New York, NY)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At Enigma we are passionate about making public data accessible. We're building beautiful, performant interfaces atop public data, and as we expand our capabilities we need frontend engineers equally capable of pushing the limits of the browser.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a front-end engineer on the platform team, you'll be responsible for building new applications, features, and data manipulation tools that haven't been seen (or even attempted) in the browser. You look at browsers as a platform, and are adept at navigating the stickier bits to make sure that both designs and functionality come out exactly as intended, regardless of browser-specific limitations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidates have&amp;nbsp;a strong grasp of the landscape of client-side frameworks and build toolchains, and insists upon implementing test coverage for everything&amp;nbsp;they do.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 16:00:20 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-07T16:00:20Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">New York, NY</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114958/front-end-engineer-for-hgtvcom-and-scripps-networks-interactive</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114958/front-end-engineer-for-hgtvcom-and-scripps-networks-interactive</link><a10:author><a10:name>Scripps Networks Interactive</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>aem</category><category>html</category><category>adobe</category><title>Front End Engineer for HGTV.com and TravelChannel.com at Scripps Networks Interactive (Knoxville, TN)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Ever thought of combining your passion of frontend engineering with your love of great lifestyle brands such as &lt;a href="http://www.hgtv.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;HGTV&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.diynetwork.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;DIY Network&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.travelchannel.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Travel Channel&lt;/a&gt; and more? Do you consider yourself a technical leader who keeps tabs on the&amp;nbsp; latest technologies yet can be pragmatic about ones that are currently used? Now's your chance to work with such award winning websites that attract more than 13 MILLION unique visitors a month at headquarters in Knoxville, Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not familiar with &lt;a href="http://www.visitknoxville.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Knoxville, Tennessee&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also been called &lt;a href="http://www.movoto.com/guide/knoxville-tn/moving-to-knoxville/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Vol Country&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.livability.com/best-places/top-100-best-places-to-live/2015?page=7" rel="nofollow"&gt;Top 100 Best Places to Live&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/places/tn/knoxville/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Forbes&amp;rsquo; Best Places for Careers&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/places/tn/knoxville/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Forbes&amp;rsquo; Most Affordable Cities&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2015/04/29/best-places-relocate_n_7163924.html" rel="nofollow"&gt;Huffington Post&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Places to Relocate to in the US&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href="http://www.knoxvilletn.gov/visitors/knoxville_info/awards_for_knoxville/" rel="nofollow"&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; goes on and on.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:49:33 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-28T21:49:33Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Knoxville, TN</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112110/ux-designer-voxy</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112110/ux-designer-voxy</link><a10:author><a10:name>Voxy</a10:name></a10:author><category>frontend</category><category>wireframe</category><category>saas</category><title>UX Designer at Voxy (New York, NY)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Voxy is changing people's lives for the better every single day. That&amp;rsquo;s not an overstatement, it&amp;rsquo;s the truth. Learning a new language is the single hardest things that you can ask an adult to do. We make it happen. Every. Single. Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voxy provides a cloud-based English language learning platform that&amp;rsquo;s based on 20 years of cutting edge scientific research into language learning. It&amp;rsquo;s proven effective, in the lab and in the wild. &amp;nbsp;Still, learning a language is incredibly hard and many never accomplish their dream. We&amp;rsquo;re working on making that a lot easier. So, we are seeking a talented UX Designer&amp;nbsp;to help people accomplish that dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You're the person that wants to join a growing start-up as we tackle the old-school entrenched players in a $60B/year industry that hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen any real innovation in decades. You're looking for a kick-ass culture, paying customers and top-tier investors; we have that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our world-class team is looking forward to hearing from you, if:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You subscribe to user centered design process.&lt;/strong&gt; You start and end with the user. While you&amp;rsquo;ve got fine-tuned instincts, you rarely waiver from identifying user personas, goals and metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You love talking to users. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;You understand the importance of getting live input and feedback from your users, and relish each opportunity you have to spend time with them, pick their brains and observe their behaviors to inform how you tackle their problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are detail-oriented and extremely organized. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;You dive into problems head first and dig until you&amp;rsquo;ve uncovered every use case and every edge case. &amp;nbsp;You are an expert at documenting findings and presenting information that is easily understood by designers, engineers and business people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You prototype. &lt;/strong&gt;You provide the right level of documentation for the task. You&amp;rsquo;re just as comfortable sketching on a whiteboard as you are with an annotated wifeframe that&amp;rsquo;s ready for developing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your world is multi-platform. &lt;/strong&gt;You recognize the difference between a user on the go and one captivate in front of a desktop. You design for them both with a perspective of the overall experience that they represent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are analytical. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;You love numbers and are comfortable manipulating raw data. &amp;nbsp;You recognize that the data rarely provides the silver bullet and are an expert at looking at disparte data and connecting the dots to paint a clear picture of the user&amp;rsquo;s experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your track record is proven. &lt;/strong&gt;You have a shipped products that are making an impact today. To get there, you translated user feedback into requirements into wireframes into features. With each product you&amp;rsquo;ve released, you can articulate the user requirements and the benefit that it delivered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your portfolio tells a story. &lt;/strong&gt;You take pride in the work you&amp;rsquo;ve done to date and know that the story of your track record is an important one that provides you the introduction to take on your next challenges. Your portfolio tells a story of how you work, why you work, and the results you&amp;rsquo;ve delivered.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 18:20:15 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-22T18:20:15Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">New York, NY</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/94188/frontend-engineer-javascript-canva</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/94188/frontend-engineer-javascript-canva</link><a10:author><a10:name>Canva</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html</category><category>css</category><category>user-interface</category><title>Frontend engineer (Javascript) at Canva (Sydney, NSW, Australia)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At Canva, we work to make a significant positive impact on society. Our mission is to democratise design. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since launch in April 2013 we have grown exponentially, and the journey has only just begun. Join Canva, and be part of this adventure. We are one of the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest growing startups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your colleagues, like you, will be the top of the industry. We mean it, when we say it is important to us that we create a workplace that you love coming to. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our culture is unlike anywhere else and our offices are designed and constantly improved to let you do great work.&lt;br&gt;At Canva you can be part of a company that is growing rapidly, building a product that users really love. You will see it on&amp;nbsp;our Twitter stream. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineering is a core part of who we are. We work hard to have a best of breed engineering culture. You will work with a carefully selected team of ex-Google, VMware, ThoughtWorks, and Atlassian engineers. Foremost; the engineering team takes pride in it&amp;rsquo;s focus and prioritisation around engineering fundamentals. The team strives to use the most appropriate tools for the tasks at hand, and to strike a measured balance between getting things done and long term maintainability. The team is tight, with no big egos, and welcome self-driven engineers to come and join in on the adventure.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 22:54:11 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-27T22:54:11Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Sydney, NSW, Australia</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/94189/java-engineer-canva</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/94189/java-engineer-canva</link><a10:author><a10:name>Canva</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>python</category><category>sql</category><category>nosql</category><category>amazon-web-services</category><title>Java engineer at Canva (Sydney, NSW, Australia)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At Canva, we work everyday to make a significant positive impact on society. Our mission is to democratise design. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since launch in April 2013 we have grown exponentially, and the journey has only just begun. Join Canva, and be part of this adventure. We are one of the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest growing startups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your colleagues, like you, will be the top of the industry. We mean it, when we say it is important to us that you love coming to work. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our culture is unlike anywhere else and our offices are designed and constantly improved to let you do great work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Canva you can be part of a company that is growing rapidly, building a product that users really love. Just check out our Twitter stream. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineering is a core part of who we are. We work hard to have a best of breed engineering culture. You will work with a carefully selected team of ex-Google, VMware, ThoughtWorks, and Atlassian engineers. Foremost; the engineering team takes pride in it&amp;rsquo;s focus and prioritisation around engineering fundamentals. The team strives to use the most appropriate tools for the tasks at hand, and to strike a measured balance between getting things done and long term maintainability. The team is tight, with no big egos, and welcome self-driven engineers to come and join in on the adventure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We run Java+Python frontends and backends, using a mix of SQL and NoSQL stores.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 22:53:51 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-27T22:53:51Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Sydney, NSW, Australia</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110653/senior-product-manager-whitepages</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110653/senior-product-manager-whitepages</link><a10:author><a10:name>Whitepages</a10:name></a10:author><title>Senior Product Manager at Whitepages (Seattle, WA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;One of our highest growth areas is our &lt;a href="http://pro.whitepages.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Pro&lt;/a&gt; business-to-business offering.&amp;nbsp; The team&amp;rsquo;s mission is to build best in class solutions to solve real world business problems they face leveraging identification and phone data we excel at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of this team, the &lt;strong&gt;Sr.&amp;nbsp;Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt; will be responsible for multiple product offerings built on top of the identification and phone data. The Sr. Product Manager will focus on diving deep into understanding our customers, their end to end journey through our products and execute on building a tailored experience that will delight them. They will work closely with every function within the team including Engineering, Sales and Marketing to build best in class products, take it to market, measure, iterate and ensure its commercial success. The role includes defining the strategy and roadmap for Pro product line including product feature definition, execution, go to market strategy, KPI definition / monitoring and then iterating over it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this role you can expect to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement, measure and iterate on user experience improvements and conversion optimizations across each of our products.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand customer needs, come up with solutions, A/B test on them 100s of times to determine the best in class experience and then bake it into the product.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain your team&amp;rsquo;s roadmap and milestones. Work with your team to estimate, implement, and build features while ensuring that you&amp;rsquo;re working on the highest priority things you can be.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage the daily workflow with a team of engineers and designers. Do whatever your team needs to help them keep moving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain a deep understanding of overall market dynamics, end user needs and competitive product capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:57:23 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-07T00:57:23Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Seattle, WA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/107713/web-application-developer-solar-technology-inc</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/107713/web-application-developer-solar-technology-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>Solar Technology Inc.</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>javascript</category><category>html5</category><title>Web Application Developer at Solar Technology Inc. (Allentown, PA) (allows remote)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;(Because of people contacting the wrong people in our organization, I have to ask that people only submit applications through Stack Overflow.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be taking over maintenance and development of the Javascript frontend and Python backend of our asset tracking web application, as well as developing new web application user interfaces for other products. After a mentoring period to help learn our products and stack of technologies, this position will grow to provide substantial independent responsibilities and a rewarding career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your development responsibilities will be varied, and include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using HTML5, CSS, and Javascript (including related libraries, including Jquery and Angularjs) to maintain and enhance the GUI of our asset tracking application. This includes both adding additional features and improving the user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using Python to query MongoDB and expose those queries as a web service.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Embedding or HTML5-based inside application wrappers for mobile platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing a featureful web user interface for our Message Board control software as an alternative to the desktop application.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 21:32:02 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-04T21:32:02Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Allentown, PA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110295/senior-front-end-engineer-at-the-sharp1-retail-quri</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110295/senior-front-end-engineer-at-the-sharp1-retail-quri</link><a10:author><a10:name>Quri</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>web-deployment</category><category>frontend</category><category>reactjs</category><category>redux</category><title>Senior Front-End Engineer at the #1 Retail Intelligence Solution at Quri (San Francisco, CA)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're looking for experienced engineers to join our small (about a dozen) but growing team of focused, dedicated, and passionate technologists who thrive using a variety of tools to solve real world business problems. Our development team is composed of experienced full stack Javascript, Rails, Python, iOS, and Android developers working with UX designers, product and sales to build our customer-facing applications. We also have a team of data engineers, analysts, and data visualization experts building a massive datastore of industry intelligence and flexible tools to power the Quri revolution. We get to build products for two very distinct and complementary user bases: our passionate on-demand Shifter community and executives at some of the world's largest brands.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:30:28 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-02T00:30:28Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">San Francisco, CA</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112964/senior-frontend-engineer-getsocial-bv</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112964/senior-frontend-engineer-getsocial-bv</link><a10:author><a10:name>GetSocial B.V.</a10:name></a10:author><title>Senior Frontend Engineer at GetSocial B.V. (The Hague, Netherlands)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Frontend Engineer to join the ongoing development of our Developer Portal and Website. You will be designing, building and shipping beautifully crafted features to delight game developers and publishers. You will be creating and maintaining the Developer Portal UI, as well as building new features that integrate with GetSocial Go / Python based backend architecture. If you are someone who has experience writing well designed, thoroughly tested and scalable web frontends, then you are the perfect candidate. Plus, you like to ask questions, you are proactive and a problem solver and prefer to collaborate instead of going alone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In return, you will work alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry. We emphasise creative problem solving, fast iteration and execution. We want to reach and have our SDK integrated by every mobile games developer on the planet, so join us and make it happen!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your role and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write modular, efficient and testable JavaScript, HTML and CSS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interface with Backend and Mobile engineering groups to deliver well integrated solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with Product managers, designers and backend engineers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactively look for ways of improving our Developers Portal and make it better&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapidly fix bugs and solve problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 13:06:43 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-05T13:06:43Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">The Hague, Netherlands</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/100500/frontend-developer-react-m-f-optiopay-gmbh</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/100500/frontend-developer-react-m-f-optiopay-gmbh</link><a10:author><a10:name>OptioPay GmbH</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html5</category><category>css3</category><category>reactjs</category><title>Frontend Developer (React) (m/f) at OptioPay GmbH (Berlin, Germany)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To develop our consumer-facing frontend with a strong focus on usability and responsiveness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To Implement frontends for our business partners and various OptioPay departments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To use HTTP/JSON APIs for communication with our backend services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To improve and maintain our live styleguide to enhance reusability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To work in a small team and collaborate with our backend developers, designers and product managers to create a great product.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To work closely with product management to develop and trial new ideas. You will gather data from use of a/b tests and other sources to facilitate decision making.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Profile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have 2+ years of relevant experience with Javascript and demonstrably good knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience of creating responsive, intuitive websites accessible from mobile, tablet and desktop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with ES6, SASS, React and Flux is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You keep track on recent trends within IT and like to explore new technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s our Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A small team of experienced developers and a complex, distributed platform to work on&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A modern technology stack with ES6, React and alt.js in the frontend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Individual responsibility and the opportunity to grow professionally&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with our founders and gain experience of an international, venture backed, startup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to a global network of successful entrepreneurs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Become part of a multinational, talented team of 30 working in Berlin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prime office location - overlooking the Spree - in the heart of Berlin&amp;rsquo;s Mediaspree&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free breakfast, drinks and fruit to keep energy levels high&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 09:07:52 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-26T09:07:52Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Berlin, Germany</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113446/full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer-nanameue-inc</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/113446/full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer-nanameue-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>Nanameue Inc.</a10:name></a10:author><category>ruby-on-rails</category><category>postgresql</category><category>mysql</category><category>redis</category><category>reactjs</category><title>Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer at Nanameue Inc. (Minato, Japan)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You will be a part of our growing web services team, report directly to our CTO and CEO and this is what you will be doing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop API backend and Web Application using Ruby on Rails + (PostgreSQL and MySQL)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build and develop&amp;nbsp;frontend part from a designer finished Sketch or PSD file using HTML/CSS and ReactJS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain test specs using Rspec and related frontend tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support and debugging web applications as needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optimize and profiling web&amp;nbsp;applications using NewRelic and related tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ignite and present a better solution to solve a problem to CTO/CEO&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Having fun and share your knowledges and visions with Junior developers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 12:15:18 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-11T12:15:18Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Minato, Japan</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/87430/frontend-developer-m-f-leipzig-germany-mynewsdesk</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/87430/frontend-developer-m-f-leipzig-germany-mynewsdesk</link><a10:author><a10:name>Mynewsdesk</a10:name></a10:author><category>reactjs</category><category>sass</category><category>javascript</category><category>twitter-bootstrap</category><category>ruby-on-rails</category><title>Frontend Developer (m/f) (Leipzig, Germany) at Mynewsdesk (Leipzig, Germany)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Department:&lt;/strong&gt; Germany&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type: &lt;/strong&gt;Full Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Min. Experience: &lt;/strong&gt;Mid Level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you like building great products?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re doing here at Mynewsdesk. And we want more people with awesome skills to join our team!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a frontend-focused developer who is passionate about building web applications with cutting edge technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is it like to work at Mynewsdesk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a workplace where you will be working in a small team, usually around five people, including developers, a designer and a product owner. All teams have their own areas of responsibility but are working together towards a common goal and an overall vision for the whole product team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The teams use the Scrum methodology, aiming to do pair or mob programming every day. Even though we have separate teams we share our knowledge and interests in cross-team meetings, internal conferences and lunch presentations. We love to learn and that&amp;rsquo;s why we have regular lab days, run a makerspace, host and attend developer conferences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;React, Bootstrap, Sass&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;MongoDB, Postgres&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heroku&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloudinary, Semaphore&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Karma, Mocha, Chai&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some of the tools we use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trello, Slack, Screenhero&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sketch, InVision, Marvel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Code Climate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keen, New Relic, Optimizely, Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip; and more&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 08:09:03 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-17T08:09:03Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Leipzig, Germany</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109949/frontend-ui-developer-m-f-optiopay-gmbh</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109949/frontend-ui-developer-m-f-optiopay-gmbh</link><a10:author><a10:name>OptioPay GmbH</a10:name></a10:author><category>html5</category><category>css3</category><category>sass</category><category>gulp</category><category>gruntjs</category><title>Frontend UI Developer (m/f) at OptioPay GmbH (Berlin, Deutschland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;To help us continuously improve our user experience, creating an intuitive, brand-consistent and engaging web interface. Yoiu will be expected to be up to date with industry best practice in web development/design; but also to analyse user data and use creative thinking to deliver tangible results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;To help improve the reliability, usability and resilience of our platform by analysing user data and being conscious of code maintainability. You will also help resolve and prevent cross-browser layout issues and bugs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;To help maintain our living styleguide, enhancing the reusability of your work and contributing to our culture of learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;With a strong focus on usability and responsiveness, develop our customer facing UI and help to develop, prototype and implement new features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Implement customised, brand-consistent frontends for our business partners and various OptioPay departments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;You will work within a small team collaborating with our backend developers, designers and product managers. You will be expected to contribute and trial new ideas; gathering data from a/b tests, user data and other sources to facilitate decision making&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Working in a small team and collaborate with our backend developers, designers and product managers to create a great product&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's our Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A small team of experienced developers and a complex, distributed platform to work on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A modern technology stack using ES6, React and alt.js in the frontend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Individual responsibility and the opportunity to grow professionally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work directly with our founders and gain experience of an international, venture backed, startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Access to a global network of successful entrepreneurs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Become part of a multinational, talented team of 30 working in Berlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prime office location - overlooking the Spree - in the heart of Berlin&amp;rsquo;s Mediaspree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Free breakfast, drinks and fruit to keep energy levels high&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 20:11:19 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-26T20:11:19Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Berlin, Deutschland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114318/senior-frontend-developer-prototype</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114318/senior-frontend-developer-prototype</link><a10:author><a10:name>Prototype</a10:name></a10:author><category>reactjs</category><category>angularjs</category><category>gruntjs</category><category>git</category><category>bower</category><title>Senior Frontend Developer at Prototype (Dubai, United Arab Emirates)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Prototype is growing and looking for a Senior Frontend web developer with experience in creating applications using JavaScript, CSS and HTML.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In your role as web developer you will create custom applications using latest technologies for a broad public audience and some of the most renowned companies in the region and internationally. This is a great opportunity to work on exciting projects by joining a team of experts in the field.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have expert skills in JS, CSS, LESS, GRUNT, NPM, ANGULAR, GIT, JADE, CMS systems and other latest web technologies then this job is for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply please send us your CV together with your answers to the questions below to jobs@prototype.ae:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tell us about yourself, your professional background and why you want to join our team at Prototype&lt;strong&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In your role as front end developer you will create cutting edge user interfaces using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This includes the utilization of frameworks such as Angular, React, lodash and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be working in a team with Producers and Backend Developers. You've been assigned to a project where you have to develop the frontend for a web application that reassembles the features of a classifieds website and where the backend is purely driven by a node.js API; please explain your approach to structure your application, explain the technologies you will use, how your development stack is setup and how you ensure the frontend is scalable, secure and organized&lt;strong&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this role we are looking for a highly skilled and experienced developer. Please tell us about the last 3 projects that are of similar in nature, what your role was, what challenges did you come across and how did you tackle them&lt;strong&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 06:52:15 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-21T06:52:15Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dubai, United Arab Emirates</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114132/senior-backend-developer-for-innovative-sap-se</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114132/senior-backend-developer-for-innovative-sap-se</link><a10:author><a10:name>SAP SE</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><title>(Senior) Backend Developer for Innovative Applications - Finance Fiori Unit at SAP SE (Berlin, Deutschland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXPECTATIONS AND TASKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Backend software development of Business applications on SAP HANA Cloud platform, as part of a talented and motivated engineering team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, test and deploy leading edge financial business applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid prototyping to analyze new technologies and software architecture alternatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write automated tests for quality assurance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Administration of continuous delivery pipeline and productive cloud infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate closely with designers, frontend developers and domain experts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS / SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Java development for business and transaction logic (J2EE etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in development of scalable cloud-based data processing systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of cloud infrastructure services (OpenStack, Docker, Cloud Foundry, AWS ELB)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion for agile software engineering (Scrum, XP, TDD etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of Cloud and Cloud technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in development of frontends for new data-driven cloud-based product&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Project experience with automated testing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of software architecture &amp;amp; design principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive knowledge of design patters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clear understanding of theoretical computer science concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent English and German language skills - written and verbal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beneficial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong focus on databases / operating systems during academic studies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of database and streaming systems (Hadoop/Spark/Flink/Kafka/Redis/Cassandra)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge of modern protocols and APIs (Protobufs/Thrift/REST/JSON/Cap'n Proto)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working in continuous delivery and continuous deployment enabled setups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with administration of build pipelines and cloud infrastructure operations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of applied statistics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript frameworks (e.g. D3.js, jQuery, &amp;hellip;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of financial accounting principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent graduates with a passion for software engineering are very welcome to apply. Please attach a list of projects you have been working on including your role, used technologies and applied development processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The position can be also filled as part time position.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 16:08:50 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-19T16:08:50Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Berlin, Deutschland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109510/web-developer-garena-online-private-limited</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109510/web-developer-garena-online-private-limited</link><a10:author><a10:name>Garena Online Private Limited</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>php</category><category>html5</category><category>javascript</category><category>linux</category><title>Web Developer at Garena Online Private Limited (Singapore)</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop mobile and desktop friendly web services using both Javascript/HTML/CSS and modern frameworks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write server-side web APIs in Python (optional)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build new features and fix bugs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build reusable code and libraries for future use&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optimization of the application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implementation of security and data protection&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write high-quality, clean, maintainable code using engineering best practices (unit testing, source control, continuous integration, automation, design patterns, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other software engineers, product managers, user experience designer, and operations engineers to build new products with web technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 04:39:33 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-23T04:39:33Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Singapore</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/80167/lead-scala-java-backend-developer-munich-mylivn</guid><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/80167/lead-scala-java-backend-developer-munich-mylivn</link><a10:author><a10:name>mylivn</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>spring</category><category>nosql</category><category>scala</category><category>java-ee</category><title>Lead Scala/Java Backend Developer (Munich, Germany) at mylivn (München, Germany)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, we are &lt;strong&gt;mylivn&lt;/strong&gt;, a young and innovative international start-up. Our key target is to become the world's largest social commerce platform. We achieve this by our own development of a high-performance platform that will transform the traditional online shopping experience to a groundbreaking modern and inspiring trading network. This basically defines our understanding of what we like to call &amp;rdquo;the future of smart shopping".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inventing products to provide richer and more interactive content on &lt;strong&gt;mylivn&lt;/strong&gt; for our users, bloggers and tradespeople is key for our daily motivation. We offer great opportunities for highly skilled talents with strong fundamental experience. We are growing fast and our target is to expand expeditiously throughout Europe, the United States and other regions around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our technology stack is mainly based on Scala and Java on the backend and Javascript, CSS, HTML on the frontend. We believe that good system designs require collaboration so that the end result is simple yet sophisticated. As a full-stack team with a very strong expertise in mobile, web, and backend developments we are currently looking for a&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lead Scala / Java Backend Developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 17:38:22 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-04-23T17:38:22Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">München, Germany</location></item></channel></rss>